(Penny:)-I'm so glad you like it.
-I do.
(Sheldon:)Leonard never cooks for me.
Well, maybe that's because
Leonard can't cook.
(Sheldon:)You can't cook and you made me this.
Whatever. Oh, let me get the cheesecake
out of the fridge.
(Sheldon:)Oh, Lord, I'm in Jewish hell.
[WOMAN MOANS ON COMPUTER]
(Raj:)Look at this. Do you think she's
really doing that or is it Photoshop?
I'm sure
Martha Stewart never got naked...
(Leonard:)...with a room full
of big fat Japanese guys.
(Raj:)You don't know that.
(Raj:)Prison changes people.
(Leonard:)Hey, where you been?
(Sheldon:)I told you. Walking.
(Leonard:)For an hour and a half?
(Sheldon:)I got lost.
(Leonard:)How could you get lost?
Your phone has GPS.